Armand G. Winfield Papers
Armand G. Winfield Papers
- Client folders
  - Norfield (#167): trips, 1972-1976; 4 folders (Box 40)
  - North American Phillips Co. (#316), 1986 (Box 40)
  - North Bay Electric Works, Inc. (#308), 1985-1986; 3 folders (Box 40)
  - O'Hory, Harry (#357), 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - ORPIA (#338), 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - Oxford Hall Silversmiths (#211), 1979; 3 folders (Box 41)
  - Parker, Brooks (#114), 1970 (Box 41)
  - Patrician Plastics Group (#18), 1964-1967 (Box 41)
  - Pentone (#28), 1965 (Box 41)
  - Petro-Chemical (#115), 1970-1971 (Box 41)
  - Plasticoid (#17), 1964-1965 (Box 41)
  - Plasticonstruction (#147), 1972-1974 (Box 41)
  - Polecats, Inc. (#57), 1967 (Box 42)
  - Population Council (#78), 1968 (Box 42)
  - Pratt Institute (#22), 1964-1970; 10 folders (Box 42)
  - Pratt Packaging (#69), 1968 (Box 43)
  - Progressive Architecture (#106), 1970; 1972; 3 folders (Box 43)
  - Prototek (#360), 1991; 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Provincial Tile Co. (#50), 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Pullman Swindell (#206), 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Pullman Swindell (#206), 1978-1979; 3 folders (Box 44)
  - Quivera, Gean (?) (#247) - missing when received, 2/2009
  - RA Marshall Imports (#44), 1966-1967; 1970-1971; 6 folders (Box 44)
  - Radetsky, Jack (#105), 1970 (Box 44)
  - Ram-Tech (#293), 1983-1985 (Box 44)
  - Ramakrishnan, R. (#212) - missing when received, 2/2009
  - Randall, Joel/Cheek, John (#222) - missing when received, 2/2009
  - Ratowsky, Ian (#299), 1985 (Box 45)
  - RC Molding Co. (#163), 1973 (Box 45)
  - Regnault, Paule (#72), 1968 (Box 45)
  - Reichhold Chemicals (#109), 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - Reid, Sara (#7), 1963-1964 (Box 45)
  - Renbrook School (#20), 1964 (Box 45)
  - Revlon, Inc. (#82), 1965 (Box 45)
  - Richards, John (#47), 1966 (Box 45)
  - Rightway Mattress Co. (#164), 1973-1974; 3 folders (Box 45)
  - Roseman, Harry (#79), 1968 (Box 45)
  - Rosen, Harry E. (#231), 1964 (Box 45)
  - Rowland Products (#5), 1964-1965 (Box 45)
  - Rubber and Technical Press, Ltd. (#162), 1963-1973 (Box 45)
  - RSZ Enterprises (#191), 1976-1977 (Box 45)
  - Salzman, Richard (#95), 1969-1970 (Box 45)
  - Sandberg, Bernard L. (#193), 1975 (Box 45)
  - Sandgren and Murtha (#119), 1971 (Box 46)
  - Sandoval, Orlando (#226), 1981 (Box 46)
  - Santa Fe Chamber of Commerce (#252), 1981 (Box 46)
  - Santa Fe Community Theater (#267), 1981 (Box 46)
  - Santa Fe Contract Design (#238), 1981 (Box 46)
  - Santa Fe Laminates, Inc. (#250), 1981 (Box 46)
  - Scwhartz/United Plastic (#132), 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Scott Plastics (#62), 1967-1968 (Box 46)
  - Selchow and Richter (#94), 1969 (Box 46)
  - Seth, Laurie (#292) - missing when received, 2/2009
  - Shapanka, H. Milton (#137), 1972 (Box 46)
  - Shell Chemical Co. (#61), 1967 (Box 46)
  - Signs of the Times (#154), 1973 (Box 46)
  - Silver City Seminar (#362), 1991 (Box 46)
  - Simpson, George (#207), 1978 (Box 46)
  - Simsovic, Jeff (#313), 1985 (Box 46)
  - Ski Wings (#302), 1985 (Box 46)
  - Slide-O-Chromse (#60), 1967-1968 (Box 46)
  - Sodalsky, Stan/Steer Skull (#242) - missing when received, 2/2009
  - SPE Albany Lectures (#34), 1965-1972; 1980; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Spencer, Elizabeth Ann (#254), 1982 (Box 47)
  - Spies, George H. (#33), 1965-66 (Box 47)
  - Stagecrafters (#356), 1990 (Box 47)
  - Sterbal, Rosewitha (#201), 1978 (Box 47)
  - Sunfield Corp. (#186), 1976-1978; 4 folders (Box 47)
  - Sunfield Corp. (#186), 1976-1977; 2 folders (Box 48)
  - Sutphin, Andrea (#338), 1988-1989 (Box 48)
  - Swingball (#142), 1972 (Box 48)
  - Systems Resources Corp. (#92), 1969 (Box 48)
  - Target Communication (#157), 1973 (Box 48)
  - Technomic Publishing Co. (#6), 1964 (Box 48)
  - Teena Creations, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 48)
  - Texas A&M University (#116), 1971 (Box 48)
  - The Clan, Inc. (#10), 1964 (Box 48)
  - The Club of Santa Fe (#314), 1985 (Box 48)
  - The Designer (#123), 1970-1971 (Box 48)
  - The Designer (#123), 1971 (Box 49)
  - Thompson, Walter J. (#192) - missing when received, 2/2009
  - Tri-State Packaging (#148), 1972 (Box 49)
  - Triborough Bridge & Tunnel Authority (#188), 1976-1977; 4 folders (Box 49)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): accessories, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): billing, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): catalog info, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): decoy data and price list, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): designs, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): flu resume data, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): general, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): labels, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): Lippe, Vincent, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): Ma-Kiwa series, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): price lists, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): NYC trip, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): Rio Madero, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): sales, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): tags & labels, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): worksheets, 1981 (Box 50)
  - Tuff-N-Lite (#248): miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 50)
  - UF Chemicals (#130), 1970-1972; 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Ultra Ten, Inc. (#272), 1983-1985; 3 folders (Box 50)
  - Ultra Ten, Inc. (#272), 1983-1985; 4 folders (Box 51)
  - UNIDO (#77): Aman, 1975 (Box 51)
  - UNIDO (#77): Colombia, 1979 (Box 51)
  - UNIDO (#77): survey of plastics, 1969; 1971; 4 folders (Box 51)
  - UNIDO (#77): travel info, 1977-1979 (Box 52)
  - UNIDO (#77): miscellaneous, 1969-1979; 6 folders (Box 52)
  - Universal Specialties (#177), 1975 (Box 52)
  - University of Arizona (#198), 1978 (Box 52)
  - University of Hartford Art School (#104), 1970 (Box 53)
  - University of Lowell (#205), 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box 53)
  - University of New Mexico (#235), 1978 (Box 53)
  - Uniwave (#185), 1976 (Box 53)
  - Veschesloff, Nadesha (#4), 1964-1969 (Box 53)
  - Verplex Co. (#52), 1966-1969; 5 folders (Box 53)
  - VH Blackinton Co. (#38), 1965-1966 (Box 54)
  - Viara Enterprises (#303), 1985-1986 (Box 54)
  - Visual Impact (#55), 1967 (Box 54)
  - Voltek, Inc. (#171), 1974 (Box 54)
  - Walsh, Joanna (#304), 1985; 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Washington Hebrew Congregation (#35), 1965-1966 (Box 54)
  - Water Jet Corp. (#301), 1985 (Box 54)
  - Water Witch/Zane Spiegel (#314), 1985 (Box 54)
  - Weber Tackle, & Plastics (#153), 1973 (Box 54)
  - Whaler, Dr. William J. (#224) - missing when received, 2/2009
  - William Kaufman Organization (#110), 1970; 12 folders (Box 55)
  - Winfield, Helen O. (#96), 1969-1970; 1974 (Box 55)
  - WM Amusements (#195), 1977-1978 (Box 55)
  - WM Amusements (#195), 1977-1978; 8 folders (Box 56)
  - Worcester Molded Products Co. (#19), 1964-1965 (Box 56)
  - Wright, Dan (#249) - missing when received, 2/2009
  - Wright Yacht Co. (#189), 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Youngerman, Jack (#203), 1978 (Box 57)
  - Zaria Displays (#3), 1964 (Box 57)
- Miscellaneous client folders
  - Air Products, 1985 (Box 57)
  - Alber, Diane, 1989 (Box 57)
  - Allai, W. Wesley, 1980 (Box 57)
  - Antique sales, 1977-1978; 1981 (Box 57)
  - Clark Museum, 1962-1963 (Box 57)
  - DuPont literature, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Engine 5030 project, 1986 (Box 57)
  - Films - Griffolyn, 1959 (Box 58)
  - Gerald Maestra's Body-Dryer, 1984 (Box 57)
  - Hoback, Priscilla, 1987 (Box 57)
  - Indian Jute Mills Association, 1972 (Box 58)
  - Lancaster merry-go-round, 1978 (Box 58)
  - National Bureau of Standards, 1971-1973 (Box 58)
  - Polyester - Celanese Corp. of America, 1957 (Box 58)
  - Porcelain enamels, frits, low temp. glass, etc., 1958 (Box 58)
  - Peng, Charlie, 1988 (Box 58)
  - Roose Electronics, 1985 (Box 58)
  - Toby Form Service, 1973 (Box 58)
  - United World College, 1984-1985 (Box 58)
- Papers
  - 100 Years Young, 1968 (Box 58)
  - Colombia: letters, 1979; 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Communications, 1969; 1975,; 1977,; 1979-1986,; 1990,; undated; 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Communications, 1973; 1976,; 1978-1979,; 1981,; 1983-1985 (Box 59)
  - Financial, 1961; 1968-1969,; 1971,; 1973-1975,; 1978,; 1980-1985,; 1987,; undated; 3 folders (Box 59)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1978-1979; 1983-1984; 3 folders (Box 59)
  - Printed materials, 1975-1980; undated; 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Printed materials, 1975-1977; 1979-1980,; 1984-1985,; 1987,; undated; 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972-1974; 1976-1981,; 1984-1985; 5 folders; photographs, handwritten notes, and sketches (Box 60)
  - Video: "CARE/Bangladesh,Winfield house", 1972; winfield_001; 1 VHS tape (Box 60)
  - Video: "The Jemez in 1939-1940, etc.", undated; winfield_002; 1 VHS tape (Box 60)